<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oh My Blog</title>
    <description>musings, rants and raves by wendi speciale
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 15:17:13 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 15:17:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Found Me</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Okay, i admit it…i was hiding…from ALL OF YOU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some days are just &lt;em&gt; easier &lt;/em&gt; than others i suppose. Whether it’s the stacks and stacks of edits i need to do at work…or the never ending list of homework assignments, or final and the most important duty i need to tend to, and that would be, ensuring my son is completing all of HIS homework assignments.  &lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 14:47:45 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2014/10/06/it's-jekyll-time.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2014/10/06/it's-jekyll-time.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Makersquare Blog Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I hate GIT. Well, it’s a love hate relationshhip. Meaning, when it does as I ask of it, i love it. When it stumps me to the point of pulling every hair out of my head, i loath it. Um, I might just be in over my head.
However, this girl loves a good challenge. It’s funny…as soon as frustration with git is about to takeover, i find myself engrossed in the process. Some people might not like learning…i happen to love it…when it is going my way. When it is not and i cannot find the answers to my questions anywhere is when I feel defeated. But then, I simply pull up Elyse’s email and she always has the answer…in a very helpful way. Love that. Really loving the journey thus far. Let’s pray i can find a way to get GIT on Team Wendi.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2014/09/21/first-makersquare-blog-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2014/09/21/first-makersquare-blog-post.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Git Outta Here</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yea. Git…as in, GIT OUTTA HERE! I struggled with it today–but stackoverflow and facebook peeps came to my rescue. Thank the Lord for all of them.I really love it when people are helpful. What i do not like is when i ask a question and someone acts put out—as if they have this entire development knowledge under their belt. Know what I think of people like that? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think they suck. 
Big time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the good news is I have a great group of people around me…Mae, Flip and Elyse are truly the bomb. It was a hard week—Tate was out sick causing me to stream from home twice this week. Not a good thing as far as catching up…but i’m doing it…and doing a pretty damn good job, if i do say so myself!
Um…i might NOT be in over my head.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2014/09/21/blog-2-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2014/09/21/blog-2-post.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
